busyagentpro.com 2011-11-02

# Privacy Policy - Terms & Conditions

**BusyAgentPro.**

**Legal Terms & Conditions** ** & Privacy Statement **

### Terms of Use

The contents of www.BusyAgentPro.com are owned by BAP and are protected by the laws of the United States, its treaty countries and other jurisdictions. You may not modify, copy, reproduce, republish, upload, post, transmit, transfer, or distribute in any way any of the contents of this website. Copyright © 1998-2009 BAP, Inc. All rights reserved. If You have created a BAP Platnum account you have agreed to these terms at the time your account was created and therefore are bound by then without exception.

### Proprietary Software

BAP develops proprietary software. You shall have no rights to this proprietary software and related documentation, or any enhancements or modifications thereto. You may not copy, transcribe, distribute, disassemble, modify, reverse engineer, create derivative works from or otherwise reduce or alter BAP Software.

Additionally, BAP may provide Clients with limited license use of its software. Clients agree and understand not to copy, transcribe, distribute, disassemble, modify, reverse engineer, create derivative works from or otherwise reduce or alter any BAP software.

### Account Cancellation Policy

The purpose of this policy is to protect the Client, as well as BAP. It prevents others from maliciously canceling a Client's account, and also provides the Client and BAP with written documentation of the Client's cancellation.

All account cancellations must be made using the automated account cancellation link in your System Profile. This can be found by clicking the "Profile" button under the calendar in your BAP desktop. You will submit the following information to submit your cancellation request.

  * Name
  * Reason for Cancellation

Once submit is pressed your account is automatically cancelled and all billing halted. BAP does not honor voicemails, fax or email requests for cancellation. 

It is important that you understand that your cancellation request will not be complete until you submit the online cancellation form.

BAP requires no long-term contracts. All accounts are billed monthly. It is the Client's responsibility to ensure that we have received the request for cancellation. We do not pro-rate any charges. You are billed according to the billing cycle that was established when your account was activated. Cancellation will occur instantly when requested; however we suggest you wait towards the end of the billing cycle to cancel your account.

Once a Client has cancelled their service, BAP will no longer provide any support to the account. This includes, but is not limited to, customer service, technical support, and domain services. (i.e.- renewals, payments, modifications, DNS alterations, etc.)

Please note that if the Client has a balance due at the time of cancellation, this balance must be paid in full. Cancellation does not absolve the Client of any outstanding financial obligations.

* * *

**Additional Privacy & General Terms & Conditions:**

**1\. GENERAL**

Platinum Memebrs agree not to use any content provided by BAP for any market othert than the markets(s) they are specifically approved for. This specifically pertainss to content that WE provide. Anyone found using content provided in the exclusive markets area for other unapproved areas either in whole or in part will be in violation of these terms and the account will be immediately terminated with no refunds given. Platinum usera are free to create custom copntent blogs and sites about other markets  

**Rrivacy Policy:  
**

**I. GENERAL**

BusyAgentPro. **** respects the privacy of every individual who visits our Web site. This Privacy Statement tells you the type of information BusyAgentPro. **** collects (Personal Information, Demographic Information, Visitor Computer Information, and Financial Information) when you visit our Web site or participate in our interactive advertisements and promotions, and how we use that information.

This Privacy Statement will also instruct you on how you can obtain copies of Personal Information you submit to BusyAgentPro., how you can verify its accuracy, and how you can request that we delete your Personal identifiable information from our databases

BusyAgentPro. **** reserves the right to amend or change any or all of the terms and conditions of this Privacy Statement by posting any such amendments or changes to this Privacy Statement. Such amendments and changes shall be effective as of the date of posting to this Web site.

**II. TYPES OF INFORMATION WE COLLECT FROM YOU**

**A. Personal Information and Demographic Information**

When you visit BusyAgentPro. **** Web sites, or participate in our interactive advertisements and promotions, we only collect Personal Information (such as name, address, telephone number, or e-mail address) and Demographic Information (such as zip code, age bracket, income bracket, education level) that you provide to us voluntarily, either about yourself or your friends or family, in response to our specific requests for you to do so.

BusyAgentPro. **** primarily uses Personal Information and Demographic Information for our internal business and marketing purposes, to enable us to better understand the interests of our customers and clients, as well as to send you information about our company, our products, and our services.

**_YOU DO NOT HAVE TO PROVIDE US WITH ANY PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION OR DEMOGRAPHIC INFORMATION THAT YOU DO NOT WISH TO DISCLOSE TO US._**

If you decide not to provide us with Personal Information or certain Demographic Information, your ability to access and view our Web sites will not be affected, but in the absence of Personal Information sufficient for us to identify you, confirm your identity, or locate you, or Demographic Information relevant to the particular interactive advertisement or promotion in which you are participating you may not be able to participate in such interactive advertisements and promotions or receive product information from us.

BUSYAGENTPRO. MAY, FROM TIME TO TIME, PROVIDE PERSONAL INFORMATION AND/OR DEMOGRAPHIC INFORMATION VOLUNTARILY SUBMITTED TO US BY VISITORS TO OUR Web site OR WHO PARTICIPATE IN OUR INTERACTIVE ADVERTISEMENTS AND PROMOTIONS TO OUR ADVERTISERS, SPONSORS, PARTICIPANT MERCHANTS, CUSTOMERS, AND CLIENTS, AS WELL AS TO THIRD PARTIES NOT AFFILIATED OR ASSOCIATED WITH BUSYAGENTPRO. WHO PROVIDE PRODUCTS OR SERVICES WHICH MAY BE OF INTEREST TO OUR CUSTOMERS AND CLIENTS.

By voluntarily providing us with Personal Information and Demographic Information, you are consenting to our use of your Personal Information as explained above.

_If you do not want us to use your Personal Information now or at any time in the future, please send a letter to our Privacy Compliance Coordinator at the address provided below._ _We will then use reasonable efforts to remove your Personal Information from our database._

_If at any time you wish to receive a copy of your Personal Information from us to review its accuracy and make any corrections, please send a letter to our Privacy Compliance Coordinator at the address provided below, and we will use reasonable efforts to supply you with your Personal Information and correct any factual inaccuracies in our database._

**Visitor Computer Information**

BusyAgentPro., like many of your favorite Web sites, may use "cookies" to collect certain information from the computer you use to access our Web site, to enable us to "recognize" your computer each time you access our Web site through it. Our cookies collect information only about your computer and how and when you use it to access our Web site. Using cookies enables us to facilitate your access to certain sections of our Web site. From time to time we may combine your Personal Information with our Visitor Computer Information to enable us to personalize your use of our Web site and make your visits even more enjoyable.

**Financial Information**

BusyAgentPro. only requests financial information, such as credit card account numbers, financial references, credit information, and the like, from visitors to our Web sites who wish to purchase products or services through our Web site. All financial transactions through our Web site are handled by secure servers which encrypt your Financial Information (and Personal Information you provide us in order to enable us to process your transaction).

BUSYAGENTPRO. STORES FINANCIAL INFORMATION AND RELATED PERSONAL INFORMATION ON ITS SECURE SERVER SOLELY TO ENABLE YOU TO ENTER INTO SUCCESSIVE PURCHASE TRANSACTIONS WITHOUT HAVING TO ENTER YOUR FINANCIAL INFORMATION FOR EACH TRANSACTION.

BUSYAGENTPRO. USES THE FINANCIAL INFORMATION AND RELATED PERSONAL INFORMATION YOU PROVIDE US ONLY IN CONNECTION WITH YOUR INDIVIDUAL PURCHASE TRANSACTIONS. WE MAY USE YOUR FINANCIAL INFORMATION AND RELATED PERSONAL INFORMATION TO CONFIRM YOUR IDENTITY AND VERIFY YOUR CREDIT WORTHINESS.

BUSYAGENTPRO. DOES NOT SHARE YOUR FINANCIAL INFORMATION OR RELATED PERSONAL INFORMATION THAT YOU PROVIDE US IN CONNECTION WITH A PURCHASE TRANSACTION WITH ANY THIRD PARTIES OTHER THAN THOSE WHO ARE OF NECESSITY INVOLVED IN THE PURCHASE TRANSACTION, SUCH AS YOUR ISSUING CREDIT CARD COMPANY, AND/OR OUR VENDOR/SUPPLIER AND/OR DISTRIBUTOR FOR THAT PARTICULAR TRANSACTION, AND THEN ONLY TO THE EXTENT NECESSARY TO COMPLETE YOUR TRANSACTION. **]**

**Employment Inquiries**

Personal Information which is submitted to us in connection with employment inquiries will be used only in the application process.

**II. Security**

BusyAgentPro. is committed to keeping secure the data you provide us and will take reasonable precautions to protect your Personal Information and Financial Information from loss, misuse or alteration.

Agents or contractors of BusyAgentPro. who have access to your Personal Information and/or Financial Information in connection with providing services to you on behalf of BusyAgentPro. are required to keep such information confidential and are not permitted to use this information for any other purpose than to carry out the services they are performing on our behalf.

Anytime you submit Personal Information or Financial Information, our secure server encrypts that information prior to your sending it to us. Additionally, we take reasonable precautions to protect your Personal Information and Financial Information stored within our systems from unauthorized access.

**III. CHILDREN**

The BusyAgentPro. Web sites are not directed to or intended for use by children 13 years of age or under ("Children" or "Child"). We do not knowingly collect Personal Information from Children. We will not knowingly accept Personal Information from Children without prior parental consent or parental notification to include an opportunity for the parent to prevent use of the information and participation in the activity. If at any time we knowingly receive Personal Information from Children without prior parental consent, we will only use that Personal Information to respond directly to such Child and our response will include a notice that we will not further communicate with such Child unless and until we receive verifiable parental consent to do so, along with information for the parent on how to contact us to either provide such consent or for further information.

**IV. CONTACTING BUSYAGENTPRO.**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Statement, this Web site, Real Estate Marketing, or if you would like further information about BusyAgentPro., you can [contact our corporate headquarters](http://www.busyagentpro.com/contact-us.html):
